<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Society on Kejun Albert Ying</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/categories/society/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Society on Kejun Albert Ying</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/categories/society/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing the Dutch elections throughout the night</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/visualizing-the-dutch-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/visualizing-the-dutch-elections/</guid>
      <description>So it&amp;rsquo;s time again for the Netherlands to have another election for the Dutch parliament (Tweede Kamer) The previous one was only in 2021, and we had elections in 2023 already for the Provinces and indirectly for the Dutch &amp;ldquo;Senate&amp;rdquo; (Eerste Kamer), but the parliamentary elections are the most important ones, usually taking place every four years (until one of the coalition partners believes they cannot support the government anymore, or if one of parties in government believe it&amp;rsquo;s in their best interest to have another election sooner rather than later).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Visualizing the State of the Amsterdam Housing Market</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/visualizing-the-state-of-the-amsterdam-housing-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/visualizing-the-state-of-the-amsterdam-housing-market/</guid>
      <description>For this post, I decided to hide the code chunks by default to improve legibility. You can click on Show code to expand the code. Introduction I&amp;rsquo;m at the age where a lot of my peers start thinking about buying a home. It is a major conversation topic around the office, and these conversations are not often filled with optimism and excitement. Oslo is a notoriously expensive city to live in, and the housing market is very tough.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
