<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>「应可钧」Kejun Albert Ying</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 「应可钧」Kejun Albert Ying</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>To-be-added</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/blog/placeholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/blog/placeholder/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Kejun Ying, postdoctoral researcher studying aging systems biology at Stanford University (Wyss-Coray lab) and Institute for Protein Design (Baker lab), NIH/NIA K00 fellow. Dr. Ying completed his Ph.D. in Biology (2025) and M.S. in Computational Science &amp;amp; Engineering (2024) from Harvard University in Dr. Vadim Gladyshev&amp;rsquo;s lab. His contributions include developing the first causal inference-based aging clock (Nature Aging cover, 2024), creating ClockBase (preprint) &amp;ndash; a platform integrating over two million biological age data highlighted in Nature Biotechnology News &amp;ndash; and developing MethylGPT, recognized in Science by Eric Topol as among the most promising biomedical large models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/cv/</guid>
      <description>Download the PDF version.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Poetry</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/poetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/poetry/</guid>
      <description>All notes are generated by AI.&#xA;The poem &#34;Hou Ting Hua Po Zi&#34; (后庭花破子) expresses the author&#39;s melancholy and despair as he reflects on the passing of time and the challenges of aging on a cold winter night. The fading starlight (&#34;寒星&#34;) and flickering candle (&#34;游烛&#34;) symbolize the waning of life. The dew-covered &#34;cui qiao&#34; (翠翘, eyebrows) and withered flowers on the colorful garment (&#34;残花附彩衣&#34;) represent the faded beauty of youth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/research/</guid>
      <description>Selection of publications. For a full list see my Google Scholar profile&#xA;2025 A Unified Framework for Systematic Curation and Evaluation of Aging Biomarkers K Ying, S Paulson, A Eames, A Tyshkovskiy, &amp;hellip;, VN Gladyshev Nature Aging&#xA;tldr: This work presents a comprehensive framework for systematically curating and evaluating aging biomarkers, addressing the challenge of standardizing the assessment of biological age measurements.&#xA;Disruption of the Cerebrospinal Fluid-Plasma Protein Balance in Cognitive Impairment and Aging A Farinas, J Rutledge, VA Bot, D Western, K Ying, KA Lawrence, HSH Oh, &amp;hellip;, T Wyss-Coray Nature Medicine</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/talks/</guid>
      <description>2025 November Biomarkers of Aging Symposium 2025 - Boston, MA&#xA;Massive AI agent mining of aging-modifying interventions from millions of molecular profiles October ASHG 2025 Annual Meeting - Boston, MA&#xA;Decoding the Aging Methylome: From Causal Inference to Foundation Models June 6th TimePie Longevity Forum - Shanghai, China&#xA;Massive AI agent mining of aging-modifying interventions from millions of molecular profiles May CSH-Asia Conference: Stem cell, Aging and Rejuvenation - Suzhou, China</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
